ROY W. REID, III

407-960-0121 | RoyReid3rd@gmail.com

Skills Summary

Team leader approaching the end of my First year with Encore. I Specialize in audio, but I've developed an understanding of additional disciplines since starting here, particularly video and lighting. I also bring extensive shipping, receiving, inventory control, and managerial experience from previous employment in other industries.

Experience

Encore Location 1609: Rosen Shingle Creek

AV Technician / June 2023 - current

Currently working at the technician level at Shingle Creek. Started primarily with set/strike work. As I've earned my tech and service certifications I've been given more opportunity to grow quickly and become a valuable asset to the team as both an operator and a leader.

Orangewood Presbyterian Church

Audio Technician/Vocalist/Camera Operator / 2012 - current

Initially started as just a vocalist but have been working on the tech side as well for the last 6 years. I've worked as an in-ear monitor operator, a camera operator for livestreams, and behind the scenes tech for DAW (Digital Performer) integration into live production.

Kroger Specialty Pharmacy

Shipping Coordinator / December 2021 - June 2023

Worked in fulfillment at a leading specialty pharmacy. Responsibilities include final verification of order accuracy, proper packaging and labeling, receiving and distributing incoming mail/packages, and maintaining the shipping dock. Actively worked with both UPS and Fedex Shipping software.

Uber Eats

Contracted Delivery Driver / January 2021 - December 2021

Worked as an uber eats driver during the Covid Pandemic.

Advent Care Center Apopka South

Materials Management Supervisor / November 2018 - March 2021

Worked as a materials management supervisor at a large nursing home facility. Personally tasked each week with providing supplies for a 200 bed facility and managing inventory.

CoolStuffinc.com

Lead Shipping Supervisor / 2016-October 2018

As a Lead Shipping Supervisor, I collaborated with management to establish a new role aimed at ensuring shipping accuracy, quality control, and operational efficiency for high-value products. Additionally, I contributed to inventory management and problem-solving initiatives, addressing issues and managing performance data, with an annual responsibility of processing over \$10,000,000 worth of products.

Education

Valencia College:

A.S. in Audio Engineering Tech partial completion

References

- Gabriel Monje Supervisor at CoolStufflnc.com 407-595-9403 -Gabriel.Monje@coolstuffgames.com
- 2. Amy Santos Supervisor at Advent Care Center Apopka South 407-412-4674 amarilys.santos@adventhealth.com
- 3. Kelvin Velez Technical Supervisor at Shingle Creek 773-339-7437 kelvin.velez@encoreglobal.com
- 4. Jack Michels Worship Director at Orangewood 407-923-9559 jmichels@orangewood.org

Additional Qualifications

- 3 years experience with computers, Word, Outlook, Excel and extensive online research at Venture lab
- 3 years experience with online retail and Google Docs at CoolStuffInc.com
- 1 year of leadership experience at CoolStuffInc.com
- Technical 100 and 200 certified. Currently working towards Tech 300 for audio.
- Professional Skills 100 and 200 certified
- Service level 100 Certified
- Experienced with Navigator from MOD shifts at Shingle
- Dante level 2 Certified
- Avid Certified user for Pro Tools